meettheboss.tv 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - MeetTheBoss

## Privacy Policy

[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) (‘the website’) is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while  
interacting with our content, products and services in a safe and secure environment.  
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we  
may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information,  
whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of,  
and your ability to correct this information. Our policy allows you to choose what  
kind of and how much information you provide to us and to control how we use  
whatever information you give us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying  
experience while allowing you to control your privacy and giving you a means to  
voice any questions or concerns you may have.

This policy applies only [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) and not to any external websites to which it is linked.

### Collection of information

Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding  
for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing,  
you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or  
information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice  
whether to respond to these questions or not.

[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) collects two types of information.  
The first type is anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth – they are ‘anonymous’ to us. Another example of the website collecting anonymous information is when users are invited to respond to surveys on [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/). The surveys may ask you for demographic information such as your age, gender and postcode. This information is collected for research purposes, is used in the aggregate (where possible) and remains anonymous. Many of the individuls who access our services are anonymous to us.

The second type of information that [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) collects is personal information. The website will collect personal information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address or postal address, when you provide it to us. With this information, [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) can provide a variety of personalised and enhanced services that are not available to anonymous users. We hope that you will find it beneficial to provide individually identifiable information about yourself to us because it will make our services more valuable to you.

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number, in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services that may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website. We may also ask about your interests, but it is your choice whether you respond.

How much of your personal information that you choose to disclose to [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us, for example when you take part in a discussion forum or enter one of the competitions on our websites.

### Use of anonymous information

[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor site use: like the numbers and frequency of visitors to the website and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) to assure that they are as appealing as we can make them for as many users as possible. [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.

### Use of personal information

[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. This may include passing that information to third party advertisers on[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) for the provision of more information about their advertising and / or promotional materials (including, but not limited to, webcasts and podcasts clearly labeled as ‘Sponsored Video’ or ‘Sponsored Podcast’. To be clear: should you choose to watch a clearly labelled ‘Sponsored Broadcast’, your contact information will be passed on to the sponsor company. [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.

### Disclosure

There will be occasions where it will be necessary for [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) to disclose your personal information to third parties. [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) may be required by law to disclose the information, or[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested. For example, if you purchase products online from [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/),[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) will need to disclose your personal information to third parties in order to bill and deliver your products. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organisation or person outside [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) unless ou have authorised us to do so. For example, when you contribute to an online forum you may want to publish your name and email address.

### Interacting with [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/)

There are many interactive features on [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/www.meettheboss.tv) that you can contribute to. These include: Forums, Reviews, Online subscriptions, Community, Mailing Lists and Email.

When interacting with [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/), we suggest that you use your discretion and exercise caution when providing your personal information.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any personal information. Be responsible whenever you are online.

### Access and correction: personal data

If [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) holds your personal information [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) will, where possible, provide you with access to the information. [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.

### Security

[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) operates secure data networks that are designed to protect your privacy and security

### Complaints about privacy

If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our websites, please notify[www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/). While [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) accepts no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will investigate all complaints.

### Changes to [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) privacy policy

If we decide to change [www.meettheboss.tv](http://www.meettheboss.tv/) Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.

### Contact details for complaints

Website Complaints Department:

MeetTheBoss TV  
Queen Square House,  
18-21 Queen Square,  
Bristol,  
BS1 4NH,  
United Kingdom.
